Seth Strouf

Web Developer

231 Manatt Ct • Lincoln, NE 68521 • seth.strouf@gmail.com • 402-418-2605 sethstrouf.com • github.com/sethstrouf/ • linkedin.com/in/sethstrouf

README

I'm an experienced professional (music education) making a big transition (software development!). I have always been passionate about both music and engineering. I am now transitioning my career from one to the other and am open to any and all professional opportunities.

PROJECTS

Portfolio

- React, Tailwind CSS Blog
- Ruby on Rails, Authentication and Authorization Memory Cards
 - React, Vanilla CSS

EDUCATION

MongoDB Basics, MongoDB University university.mongodb.com/

The Odin Project theodinproject.com/ November 2019—February 2020 Foundations and Full Stack Ruby on Rails

University of Helsinki, Java Programming java-programming.mooc.fi/ June 2015-July 2015

University of Nebraska, Lincoln, NE June 2014–July 2017 Master of Music, Education

Doane University, Crete, NE August 2006—May 2010 B.A., Music Education and Vocal Performance

SKILLS

HTML & CSS
JavaScript
Ruby on Rails
React
Tailwind CSS
Communication
Problem-Solving
Teamwork

EXPERIENCE

Crete Public Schools 6-12 Vocal Music Director August 2021—Present

Raymond Central Schools K-12 Vocal Music Director August 2010-May 2021

EXTRACURRICULARS

Professional Choirs

National Association for Music Education

American Choral Directors Association

College Computer Club President

National FBLA Competitions (C++, Java, Visual Basic)